# SEAN FISHER

DATA ANALYST

seanfisher1218@gmail.com



(805) 990-6654



San Diego, CA 92122



# **EXPERIENCE**

# Modern Analytics - Data Engineer Intern / Consulting

San Diego, CA • 01/2023 - Present

- Optimized data processing by implementing efficient data pipelines and automating workflows.
- Executed comprehensive data analysis for actionable insights and improving operations.
- Designed and developed analytical data structures using Python and SQL.
- Utilized SQL queries to extract relevant information from large databases.

# Volunteer Income Tax Assistance (VITA) - Tax Preparation Intern

Simi Valley, CA • 01/2019 - 04/2019

- Gained practical experience with relevant software and technology.
- Participated in training sessions and workshops to enhance knowledge and skillset.
- Gathered data on taxable income, deductibles, and allowances for tax preparation.
- Maintained confidentiality when handling sensitive information or documents.

# **Regents Pizzeria - Customer Service Representative**

San Diego, CA • 09/2021 - Present

- Developed strong customer relationships and loyalty through effective communication.
- Maintained an updated knowledge base of current products, services, pricing, promotions.
- Assisted with training and mentoring new team members.

# **SKILLS**

- Analytical Thinking
- Computational Skills
- Data Cleaning
- Data Modeling
- Data Pipeline Design
- Data Pre-Processing
- \* Data Visualization
- \* Feature Engineering
- \* Predictive Analytics
- \* Project Base Programming
- \* SQL Programming
- \* Time Management

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Python (Pandas, Scilearn, Matplotlib), Tableau, R Programming, LaTeX, Excel, javascript, Google Docs, Microsoft 365, Overleaf, Sublime Text.

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven professional with experience in Snowflake, SQL, Python and Excel for data extraction. Experienced in creating data pipelines and visualizations. Strong analytical skills and problem-solving abilities. Deep understanding of database technologies. Equally confident working independently or in collaboration as part of a team. Adhering to honesty and integrity are strong core values.

## **EDUCATION**

University of California, San Diego La Jolla, CA • 06/2023

Bachelor of Science (B.S.): Mathematics

#### **Relevant Coursework**

- Actuarial Mathematics
- Data Analysis and Interference
- Cryptography
- Probability Theory

# **University of California, San Diego**

La Jolla, CA • 06/2023

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.): Economics

## **Relevant Coursework**

- Macroeconomic Data Analysis
- Business and Forecasting
- Operations Research
- Micro/Macroeconomics & Econometrics
- Decisions Under Uncertainty

# **Moorpark College**

Moorpark, CA • 05/2020

# Associate in Science (A.S.):

Business Administration (Honors Program)

## **Moorpark College**

Moorpark, CA • 05/2020

## Associate in Arts (A.A.):

Economics (Honors Program)

# **REFERENCES UPON REQUEST**